[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'のります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Їздити"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'でんしゃにのります' read in word?",
        "answer": "сідати на поїзд"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'のりかえます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Робити пересадку"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かえます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Міняти"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'シャワーをあびます' read in word?",
        "answer": "приймати душ"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'はいります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вступати"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'だいがくをでます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Закінчити"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'やめます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Звільнятися, кидати"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Натискати"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'あたま' read in word?",
        "answer": "Голова"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かみ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Волосся"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かお' read in word?",
        "answer": "Обличчя"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'め' read in word?",
        "answer": "Очі"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'みみ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вухо"
    }
]